而那就是为什么  不管妈咪说什么
And that's why,no matter what Mommy says..
我们都真的暂时分手了  是的  没错
we really were on a break. Yes,we were.
是的  没错  来吧  漂亮宝贝
Yes,we were. Come here,gorgeous.
瞧瞧你  你是史上最可爱的小宝宝了
Look at you. You are the cutest little baby ever.
你只是个小不点婴儿  知道吗
You're just a little-bitty baby,you know that?
但是你拥有
But you've got..
你拥有大大漂亮的双眼
You've got big,beautiful eyes.
是的  没错
Yes,you do.
还有  还有大大圆圆的肚肚
And a.. And a big,round belly.
大大的婴儿屁屁
Big baby butt.
我喜欢大屁屁
I like big butts.
我喜欢大屁屁  我无法说谎
I like big butts and I can not lie
其他的兄弟无法否认
You other brothers can't deny
一个有着小蛮腰的女孩走进来
when the girl walks in with an itty bitty waist
圆滚滚  贴着你的脸
And a round thing in your face
你就
You get...
噢  天啊  艾玛  你在笑
Oh,my God,Emma. You're laughing.
我的天  你从没有这样过  对吗
Oh,my God. You've never done that before,have you?
你从来没有这样过
You've never done that before.
爹地逗你笑了  对吧
Daddy made you laugh,huh?
嗯  是爹地还有"混音老爹"
Well,Daddy and Sir Mix-A-Lot.
什么  什么  你还想听更多是吗
What? What? You wanna hear some more?
我真是个糟糕的父亲
I'm a terrible father.
-你们懂得投资吗  -怎么了
- What do you know about investments? - How come?
我演的剧开始让我赚到一些钱了
I'm starting to make good money on the show,
所以我想我应该好好利用那些钱
and I should do something with it.
那你现在把钱放在哪里呢
What do you do with your money now?
藏在我家马桶水箱后面
It's taped to the back of my toilet tank.
我没有那样说
I didn't say that.
是放在银行由机器人看守着
It's in a bank guarded by robots.
你有什么想法吗
Do you have any ideas?
有个同事的提议让我觉得很兴奋
A guy at work got me excited..
是关于投资鸸鸟农场  很酷吧
about going in on an emu farm. That'd be kind of cool,huh?
在周末的时候过去帮忙
Pitching in on the weekends,
帮助种植鸸鸟
helping to plant the emus.
乔伊  鸸鸟是鸟类
Joe,emus are birds.
是养来当食物的
You raise them for meat.
嗯  是噢
Yeah. Right!
人类会吃小鸟  小鸟肉
People eat birds. Bird meat.
他们是直接飞进你的嘴里吗
Do they just fly into your mouth?
还是你可以到餐厅说
Or you go in a restaurant and say:
"不好意思  我要点一份炸鸟"
"Excuse me,I'll have a bucket of fried bird."
或是一个翅膀  或是
Or maybe just a wing. Or a.
乔伊  我觉得你应该考虑
Joey, I think you should consider
比较低风险性的投资
something a little less risky.
我认为在当前市场
I think in this market
房地产会是最好的投资
real estate is your best investment.
联邦储备银行才刚降息
The Fed just lowered the rates,
而且房贷的利率也可以扣减所得税额
and the interest on your mortgage is totally deductible.
没错  我懂的挺多的
That's right. I know some stuff.
房地产  是吗
Real estate,huh?
你知道谁要卖一间很棒的公寓吗  理查
And you know who's selling a great apartment? Richard!
你知道谁对她前男朋友的熟悉度
And you know whose knowledge of her ex-boyfriend
很吓人吗  莫妮卡
is shocking? Monica!
我爸告诉我的  他们一起打高尔夫球
My dad told me. They play golf together.
那么  或许我应该加入他们
Well,maybe I'll join them sometime.
我只希望球杆不要滑出我的手
I just hope the club doesn't slip out of my hand..
然后把他的八字胡从他脸上打掉
and beat the mustache off his face.
听着  你们要帮我选衣服
Listen, You have to help me pick a dress.
我今晚要跟麦克的父母见面
I'm meeting Mike's parents tonight.
哇  男朋友的父母亲  真是一大步
Wow,the boyfriend's parents. That's a big step.
真的吗  我倒是没有这样想过
Really? That hadn't occurred to me.
他们会喜欢你的  自然随性就好
They are gonna love you. Just be yourself.
他们住在上东区的公园大道
They live on the Upper East Side on Park Avenue.
那她就不能自然随性了
Yeah,she can't be herself.
好了  那么  哪一件呢
Okay,so,all right,which dress?
你们可以说都不好
You can say neither.
噢  天啊  都不好
Oh,God. Neither.
我很抱歉  我们会带你去买衣服
I'm sorry. We'll take you shopping.
没事的
It'll be fine.
绝对的  相信我们的眼光吧
Totally, you are in such good hands,
我很擅长应对见父母这类事
and I am so good with meeting parents.
面对他父亲  稍微打情骂俏一下
With the father,you wanna flirt a little,
但是不要太恶心
but not in a gross way.
可以像是  "品瑟先生
Just kind of like,"Mr. Pinzer,
我现在终于知道
I can see
华勒斯帅气的长相是遗传谁的了"
where Wallace gets his good looks."
你跟华勒斯·品瑟交往过
You went out with Wallace Pinzer?
他替我考过高考
He took the SATs for me.
我就知道你没有考过1400分
I knew you didn't get a 1400!
是啊  当然了  我是说
Yeah,well,duh! I mean..
那麦克的妈妈怎么办呢
So now,what about with Mike's mom?
至于他母亲
Well,with the mother,
只要不断的告诉她
just constantly tell her
她儿子有多棒就行了
how amazing her son is.
以我为例  母亲们都很喜欢我
Take it from me. Moms love me.
罗斯的妈有一次甚至还说
Ross' mom one time actually said..
我就像是她从未有过的女儿
I am like the daughter that she never had.
她说什么
She said what?
她就像是她从未有过的女儿
She's like the daughter she never had.
听好了
Listen.
我才帮菲比打扮好
I just finish getting Phoebe all dressed
让她去见麦克的父母
to meet Mike's parents.
她好紧张  真是太感人了
She's so nervous. It's so sweet.
猜猜怎么着  我今天逗艾玛笑了
Guess what. I made Emma laugh today.
你什么  我竟然错过
You what? And I missed it..
都是因为要帮那愚蠢的嬉皮改变造型
because I was giving a makeover to that stupid hippie?!
是啊  而且就像是小大人的笑噢
Yeah,and it was like a real little person laugh too.
就像是
It was like:
只不过不像这样吓人
Only not creepy.
-你做了什么逗她笑  -我
- What did you do to make her laugh? - I..
嗯  我唱了歌  其实
Well,I sang. Actually..
是饶舌歌
I rapped..
《宝贝背后好身材》
"Baby Got Back."
你什么
You what?
你对着我们的宝贝女儿唱
You sang to our baby daughter..
一首关于男人想要搞一个
a song about a guy who likes to have sex..
大屁股女人的歌
with women with giant asses?
其实  如果你仔细想想
You know what,if you think about it..
它事实上是在提倡健康的身体观念
it actually promotes a healthy body image..
因为即使是大屁股
because even big butts..
或是"可口多汁的双乳"都是
or "juicy doubles" are..
请不要把她从我身边带走
Please don't take her away from me.
嗨  请进 我是凯瑟琳  仲介商
Hi,come on in. I'm Catherine,the listing agent.
嗨  我是乔伊  他是钱德勒
Hi,I'm Joey. This is Chandler.
为什么理查要卖掉这地方呢
So how come Richard's selling the place?
破产了吗
Went bankrupt?
医疗误诊  被自己的胡子噎死吗
Medical malpractice? Choked on his own mustache?
事实上他要买一间更大的公寓
Actually he's buying a much bigger place.
景观很棒  可以看到中央公园
It's got a great view of Central Park..
你说够了
That's enough out of you.
这地方有什么我们需要知道的吗
Is there anything we should know about the place?
电器用品全部都包含
All the appliances are included.
光线充足  还有新的厨房
There's a lot of light,a new kitchen.
我想你们俩住在这里一定会很幸福
I think you guys would be very happy here.
不
No.
不  我们没有在一起
No,we're not together.
我们不是一对
We're not a couple
我们绝对不是一对
We're definitely not a couple.
-好的  抱歉  -没关系
- Okay. Sorry. - That's all right.
哇  你看起来好像是被侮辱了一样
Wow,you seemed pretty insulted by that.
是怎样  我配不上你吗
What,I'm not good enough for you?
我们不要再讨论这个问题了
We are not gonna have this conversation again.
瞧瞧这地方
Look at this place.
我为什么备受这家伙的威胁呢
Why am I so intimidated by this guy?
矫情的艺术品  又大又阳刚的沙发
Pretentious art. This huge,macho couch.
我们知道他整天只会坐在那边
When we know all he does is sit around all day..
哭泣着为什么莫妮卡会离开他
crying about losing Monica
投入一个真男人的怀抱
to a real man.
他应该不在这里吧  对吗
You don't think he's here,do you?
这是个好地方  但是我必须要说
You know, It's a nice place,but I gotta say,
我不知道我能不能住得习惯
I don't know if I see myself living here.
让我们来试试看
Well,let me see.
是的  我可以住得习惯
Yeah,I can see it.
瞧瞧这些录影带  他以为他是谁啊
Look at these videos. I mean,who does he think he is?
《紧急搜捕令》 《肮脏哈里》 《铁窗喋血》
Magnum Force,Dirty Harry,Cool Hand Luke.
-噢  我的天  -怎么了
- Oh,my God. - What?
有一卷带子上面有莫妮卡的名字
There's a tape here with Monica's name on it.
有一卷带子上面有女生的名字
A tape with a girl's name on it.
可能是性爱录影带
It's probably a sex tape.
等一下
Wait a minute.
上面写着"莫妮卡"
This says "Monica."
而这里是理查的公寓
And this is Richard's apartment.
快点说
Get there faster!
哇  你看起来
Wow. You look..
真像我妈
like my mom.
我有穿丝袜
I'm wearing pantyhose.
-太棒了  请进  -好的
- Great! Come on in. - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
噢  我的天  你真有钱
Oh,my God. You're rich.
不  是我父母亲有钱
No,my parents are rich.
那又如何  他们总会死的
Well,so? They gotta die someday.
你好
Hello!
爸妈  这是菲比
Mom,Dad,this is Phoebe.
菲比  他们是我父母 希尔多和贝西
Phoebe,these are my parents,Theodore and Bitsy.
希尔多  贝西
Theodore,Bitsy..
很高兴能与你们见面
what a delight.
真高兴  终于见到你了
It's so nice to finally meet you.
彼此彼此
And you.
你们家真是美好
Your home is lovely.
谢谢  等一下我可以带你参观
Thank you. I'll give you a tour later.
其实总共有三层
It's actually three floors.
我的妈啊
Holy crap!
菲比  过来客厅见见我们的朋友吧
Phobe, Why don't you come meet our friends.
非常荣幸
Try and stop me.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
试着让你父母亲喜欢我
Trying to get your parents to like me.
我相信他们会的  但是你不用这样假
I'm sure they will,but you don't have to do this.
我要他们认识真正的菲比
I want them to get to know Phoebe,
不是装出来的"菲比"
not "Phoebe."
-知道了 -好了
- You've got it. - All right.
很难停止
It's hard to stop.
好了  来吧
Well,come on.
菲比  来见见我们的朋友
Phoebe,these are our friends
汤姆和苏安格
Tom and Sue Engel.
菲比  来坐下
Phoebe,come sit.
跟我们介绍一下你自己
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
-你是哪里人呢  -好的
- So where are you from? - Okay.
嗯  好的  我本来是上州人
Well,all right. Originally,I'm from upstate..
但是后来我妈自杀
but then my mom killed herself,
然后继父去坐牢
and my stepdad went to prison.
所以我就搬到市里
So I moved to the city,
在一辆被火烧过的车里住过一阵子
where I lived in a burned-out Buick LeSabre for a while.
那倒是没关系  还好啦
Which was okay. That was okay.
直到我染上肝炎  你知道的
Until I got hepatitis,you know..
因为有个皮条客吐口水到我嘴里  然后
because this pimp spit in my mouth and..
但是我已经好了
But I got over it.
然后  反正
And,anyway,
现在我是自由按摩治疗师
now I'm a freelance massage therapist..
赚的钱不是很稳定
which isn't always steady money,
但至少不用缴税
but at least I don't pay taxes.
那大家都到哪度暑假呢
So where does everyone summer?
噢  天啊  真是进行的不顺利
Oh,God,this is not going well.
不  你做的很好  真的
No,you're doing fine. Really.
你何不去找我爸聊聊
Why don't you go talk to my dad.
好  好的  好的
Okay,okay,okay.
你依然确定要我表现真实的自己吗
Still sure about me being myself?
当然
Absolutely.
或许少说一些"皮条客吐口水"的事
Though maybe just a little less "pimp spit."
希尔多  我现在知道
So,Theodore,I can see
麦克的帅气外表是遗传自谁的了
where Mike gets his good looks from.
你一定经常做运动
You must work out all the time.
不是很常  不过是尽量而已
Not all the time. I do the best I can.
是啊  我想也是  看招
Yeah,I bet. Look out!
噢  我的天  你还好吗
Oh,my God. Are you okay?
我最近刚动完手术
I recently had surgery.
-我很抱歉  -没关系  我没事
- I'm so sorry. - No,I'll be fine.
我只是  应该去检查一下伤口
I just should check the stitches.
我真的很抱歉
I really really am sorry.
你怎么会知道呢
How could you know?
你"当然不会"打我的肚子
Why wouldn't you punch me in the stomach?
你刚刚是不是打了我爸
Did you just hit my dad?
是的  我很抱歉
Yes. I'm sorry.
我从来没有见过男朋友的父母亲
I've never met a boyfriend's parents before.
但是  你总该见过人  对吗
But,I mean,you have met humans before,right?
你何不去找我妈聊聊
Why don't you go talk to my mom.
好的  你妈  好的
Okay,yeah,your mom. Ok.
她看起来很和善  我可以跟她聊的
She looks nice. I can talk to her.
是啊  你去吧  我要去看看
Yeah. You do that,and I'm gonna go check
我爸是不是有内出血的现象
my dad for signs of internal bleeding.
贝西  我想要再次谢谢你
Bitsy? Listen,I wanted to thank you again
邀请我今晚过来
for having me here tonight.
噢  不用客气
Well,not at all.
还有  我只想让你知道
Also,I just want you to know
你儿子是个很棒的男人
what a wonderful man your son is.
谢谢  我也这么认为
Thank you. I think so too.
一切都是他受了良好的家庭教育
It's a testament to how he was raised.
尤其是你的功劳
Especially to you,
因为他十分尊重女性
because he's very respectful of women.
他真的吗
Is he really?
开什么玩笑  他非常体贴我的感受
Are you kidding? He is so considerate of my feelings.
我认为你也会想知道
You know,I think you'd also like to know
他在床上非常温柔
that he is a very gentle lover.
什么
Excuse me?
不  别误会我
No,don't get me wrong.
不  不是那种娘娘腔的样子
No, he is not in like a sissy way.
不是  不是  当他疯起来的时候
No, no, When he gets going..
他可是像休假的船员一样神勇
he can rattle a headboard like a sailor on leave.
真不愧是  我儿子
That's.. my boy.
真了不起
Awesome.
我不会看的  我不需要看
I'm not gonna watch it. I don't need to watch it.
我是说  看了又有什么好处呢
I mean,what good could possibly come from watching it?
我们知道我还是要看的
Well,we know I'm gonna watch it.
嘿  兄弟  怎么了
Hey,dude,what's up?
别评判我  我只不过是个普通人
Don't judge me! I'm only human!
你私自偷走了那卷带子吗
Did you take that tape?
我是不得已  假设你结婚了
I had to! OK? Imagine you were married
然后你发现一卷你老婆的录影带
and you found a tape of your wife..
在另一个男人的公寓里
in another guy's apartment.
你难道不想知道里面是什么吗
Wouldn't you need to know what was on it?
我不知道  我跟谁结婚呢
I don't know. Who am I married to?
某个女孩
Some girl.
她性感吗
She hot?
她是怎么让我定下来的
How did she get me to settle down?
好了  我要看
All right,I'm gonna watch it.
我是说  或许根本不是我想的那样
I mean,it's probably not even what I think it is.
即使是  或许也不像我现在脑海中
Even if it is,it can't possibly be
想像的情景那样糟糕
as bad as what I'm picturing in my head.
会吗
Can it?
依据我的经验
Settle on my experience,
如果女生答应可以录下来
if a girl says yes to being taped..
其他的基本也不会拒绝了  我跟你说
she doesn't say no to much else,I'll tell you.
-那你先帮我看  -什么
- Then you have to watch it for me. - What?
几秒钟就好  让我知道那是什么
Just for a few seconds so I can know what it is.
拜托
Please?
好啦  可以
All right,fine.
但是万一我乐在其中
But if I enjoy this,
你就只能怪你自己
you have only yourself to blame!
为什么我听到欢呼声
Why am I hearing cheering?
没关系  是橄榄球赛
It's okay. It's just a football game.
橄榄球  只是橄榄球赛吗
Football? It's just football?
你担心是多余的
You were all worried for nothing.
是橄榄球赛  只是是橄榄球赛
It's football! It's just football!
太棒了
This is great!
这是我第一次真正喜欢橄榄球
This is the first time I've ever enjoyed football!
我想这时候喝啤酒很对味
I think it may be customary to get a beer.
搞什么
What the..?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你不想要看到我刚看到的东西
You don't wanna see what I just saw!
你们在做什么
What are you guys doing?
噢  我的天  那是理查吗
Oh,my God! Is that Richard?
好了  给妈咪笑一笑  拜托
Okay,please laugh for Mommy. Please?
请为妈咪笑一个
Please laugh for Mommy.
不好笑  对吧
Not funny,huh?
是不是...
Well,so is it..
只有低级好玩的饶舌歌才行呢
only offensive novelty rap?
或许只要是饶舌歌都行
Or maybe just,you know,rap in general.
因为妈咪会饶舌噢
Because Mommy can rap.
我的名字叫妈咪
My name is mommy
我想告诉你
And I'm here to say
所有的宝宝都
That all the babies are
我不会饶舌
I can't rap.
好了  亲爱的
All right,sweetheart.
那只是因为我太爱你了
This is only because I love you so much.
而且我知道你不会告诉别人
And I know that you're not gonna tell anybody.
我喜欢  大屁屁  我无法说谎
I like big butts and I can not lie
其他的兄弟无法否认
You other brothers can't deny
一个有着小蛮腰的女孩走进来
when the girl walks in with an itty bitty waist
圆滚滚  贴着你的脸
And a round thing in your face
太棒了  太棒了
Yes! Yes! Yes!
我喜欢  大屁屁  我无法说谎
I like big butts and I can not lie
其他的兄弟无法否认
You other brothers can't deny
艾玛  你在笑  你笑了
Emma,you're laughing! You are!
你真的很喜欢大屁屁  对不对
You really do like big butts,don't you?
你这个漂亮的小怪蛋
You beautiful little weirdo.
你错过了  她刚刚在笑
You missed it! She was laughing!
真是不可思议
It was amazing.
真不可思议
那简直是最美妙的声音
It was the most beautiful,beautiful sound.
我知道  可不是吗
I know,isn't it?
你做了什么逗她笑
What'd you do to get her to laugh?
其实  我只不过试了一些东西  不同的
You know,I just.. A couple of things I tried. Different..
只是唱了一点《痒痒小蜘蛛》
Just sang a little "The Itsy-Bitsy Spider."
你唱了《宝贝背后好身材》对不对
You sang "Baby Got Back," didn't you?
其它的方法都没有用
Nothing else worked!
我们家女儿就是喜欢屁屁
That girl is all about the ass!
然后再回到副歌部分
And then it goes back to the chorus.
然后那就是歌曲的结尾
And that's the end of the song.
我知道你们没有要我唱
I realize you hadn't asked to hear it..
但是已经有17分钟没有人说话了
but no one had spoken in 17 minutes.
菲比创作了许多很棒的歌曲
Phoebe writes lots of great songs.
你那天晚上唱的歌是什么
What was that one you sang the other night
大家都很喜欢的那首
that everybody just loved?
《变态游行》吗
"Pervert Parade"?
-《阴毛颂》吗  -停止
- "Ode to a Pubic Hair"? - Stop.
噢  天啊  这是小牛肉吗
Oh,God. Is that veal?
妈  我以为我跟你说过
Mom,I thought I told you,
菲比是素食者
Phoebe's a vegetarian.
不  没关系  没关系
No,that's okay. That's okay.
我是说  我是素食者
I mean,I am a vegetarian..
不过我吃小牛肉 是的  我爱吃小牛肉
except for veal. Yeah. No. Veal I love.
菲比  你可以不用吃的
Phoebe,you don't have to eat that.
不不不  事实上
No, no, no, actually
我喜欢任何小动物肉  小猫咪肉  小鱼
Any baby animals. Kittens,fish babies.
但是  尤其喜欢小牛肉
But,you know,especially veal.
这上面还有带一点很棒的肥肉
You know,and this nice vein of fat running through it.
好吃
Yummy.
那
So..
你们觉得如何呢
what do you think?
所以你从理查的公寓偷了这卷带子
So you stole that tape from Richard's apartment?
听听  色情片明星竟然在批评我
Listen to the judgment from the porn star!
那带子本来就不该让
That tape was never meant to be seen by..
乔伊  我希望可以
Joey,I would feel more comfortable
私下谈论这件事
if this conversation were in private.
莫妮卡  听着  我不认为
Monica,look,I don't think
你我之间存在任何秘密了
you and I have any secrets anymore.
没到以此事开玩笑的时候吗
Not ready to joke about it yet?
那好吧  待会见
Ok, I'll see you later.
你为什么要拿这卷带子呢
Why in the world would you take this tape?
而且为什么要看呢
And why would you watch it?
因为我就是这样的人  好吗
Because that's who I am. Okay?
我相信像理查那样成熟的男人
I'm sure a man like Richard
可以看这样的带子  而且不会被说教
could see a tape like that and not be bothered.
那只不过是个黄色小插曲
It'd just be another saucy anecdote..
让他可以在男性俱乐部里
for him to share at his men's club
喝着白兰地  摸着胡子  和兄弟们分享
over brandy and mustaches.
你闹来闹去  就因为你不能长胡子吗
Is all of this about you not being able to grow a mustache?
此事是跟你和理查有关
This is about you and Richard.
他明显没有忘记你
He's clearly not over you.
他保留这带子
He keeps a tape
是为了在任何想看的时候就看
so he can look at it whenever he wants.
那不是很可悲吗
Isn't that sad?
你看不出来这是多可悲的事吗
Can't you see how pathetic that is?
别吃醋了  你应该为他感到可怜
Don't be jealous. You should feel bad for him.
是啊  可怜的理查  他
Yeah,well,poor Richard,he..
我可以长胡子的
I can grow a mustache.
钱德勒  这不是我们的问题
Chandler, this is not our problem.
我们拥有彼此  这才是最重要的
We have each other. That's all that matters.
是啊  但我老想着
Yeah, but I just keep picturing
你和他在床上滚来滚去
you rolling around with him,
穿着你的
with your..
牛仔靴在空中晃来晃去
cowboy boots in the air.
牛仔靴
Cowboy boots?
我这辈子从没有穿过牛仔靴
I've never worn cowboy boots in my whole life.
很好  非常好
Good,good.
再多放一点  我想看结局是怎样
Play more because I wanna see how it ends.
-那不是我  -什么
- That's not me! - What?
那不是你  美好的生活又再度来临了
That's not you! Life is good again!
骑上去  牛仔女
Ride 'em,cowgirl!
那混蛋洗了我的带子录别人
That bastard taped over me!
那有什么问题吗
Is that a problem?
真是太侮辱人了
It's just so insulting.
花钱买新的空白带子嘛  医生
Spring for a new blank tape,doctor!
我不明白他到底看上她什么了
I can't imagine what he sees in her.
她真让我怀念起他那嗜药的前妻
She actually makes me miss that pill-popping ex-wife of his.
嗨  亲爱的
Hello,dear.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们只是随便聊聊
We were just chitchatting.
-你的朋友还好吗  -好一点了
- How's your friend? - A little better.
顺便问下  你知道谁要搬回城里了吗
By the way, do you know who's moving back into town?
汤姆跟苏的女儿  珍
Tom and Sue's daughter,Jen.
你知道她的  麦克
You remember her,Michael.
她很可爱  举止端庄  而且单身
She's lovely,well-behaved and single.
我没有兴趣
I'm not interested.
拜托  亲爱的  老实说吧
Please,darling,let's be honest.
你跟她也可以享受水手般的激烈性爱的
You can have all the sailor fun you want with that one.
-但是我们要面对现实  -好了  停
- But let's be real. - All right,stop.
菲比今晚所做的一切
All Phoebe has done tonight
都是为了要让你们喜欢她
is try and get you to like her.
或许你们没看出她的意图
Maybe it hasn't been clear all the time
但是她已经尽力而为了
but she did her best.
她是跟你们有点不同
She's a little different than you are.
麦克  一个皮条客吐口水在她嘴里
Michael,a pimp spit in her mouth.
那又如何  如果我都无所谓了
So what? If I can get past that,
你们有什么好在意的
it shouldn't bother you.
你们没必要去喜欢她
You don't have to like her.
只需要接受我喜欢她的事实就可以
Just accept the fact that I do.
如果你们无法善待我爱的女人
If you can't even be civil to the woman I love..
你什么的女人
The woman you what?
是啊  你什么的女人
Yeah,the woman you what?
我爱的女人
The woman I love.
我爱你
I love you.
不过我第一次对你说这句话
Just something I probably shouldn't say for the first time,
或许不该当着我父母的面
in front of my parents..
以及汤姆跟苏的面
and Tom and Sue.
对了  顺便说一句
Who are,by the way,
他们是我一生中遇过的最无聊的人
the most sinfully boring people I've ever met in my life.
-我也爱你  -真的吗
- I love you too. - You do?
多棒啊
How great is this?
-想要离开这里吗  -好的
- Wanna get out of here?  -Ok
爸妈  谢谢你们的晚餐
Mom,Dad. Thanks for dinner.
我玩得很开心
I had a great time.
这里真的很高级  而且更棒的是
It was really top-drawer. And here's something rich.
屋里有13间洗手间
Thirteen bathrooms in this place,
但我却吐在衣帽间里面
I threw up in the coat closet.
别了
Ta-ta!
大汗淋漓  香湿润滑
She's Sweat,Wet,
屁屁像涡轮一样疯狂摇摆
got it goin like a turbo vette
兄弟们  兄弟们
Fellas, Fellas,
你的女朋友有大屁股吗
Has your girlfriend got the butt
当然了
Hell yeah.
扭起来吧  扭起来吧
So shake it, shake it
扭起那健康的大屁股
shake that healthy butt
宝贝背后好身材
Baby got back
从头再来一次
One more time from the top!
我喜欢大屁屁  我无法说谎
I like big butts and I can not lie
其他的兄弟无法否认
You other brothers...
瑞秋  拜托  实在太少儿不宜了
Rachel,please! That is so inappropriate!